

Flutter Developer

Huzaifa Khan

Professional summary

I am a full stackFlutter developer with almost 1.5 years of Professional experience. I have one App deployed on Google play store, have strong problem-solving skills and love to learn new things in my field such as Mobile Application Development (Flutter).

Experience

Full stack Flutter Developer

October 2023 - January 2024 SoftThrive / Pakistan, Rawalpindi

Flutter, Firebase

Internships

Flutter Intern

July 2022 - September 2022 CapregSoft / Pakistan, Wah Cantt, Taxila

Java Basics and Postgresql

July 2023 - September 2023

Pakistan Ordenance Factories (POF) / Pakistan, Wah Cantt

Certifications

Flutter 2x, C Sharp, GitHub, SQL, IELTS, HTML, JavaScript, NodeJS

Live Applications

Password Saver

United States

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.softmostro.password_saver

General Skills

Java, JavaScript, NodeJS, C sharp, C and C++, Python, MYSQL, SQL lite, AWS(EC2), MongoDB

+92 318 0794547

hk7928042@gmail.com

🔾 Pakistan, Rawalpindi, Wah Cantt

Links

in huzaifak08

nuzaifak08 🕝

Education

Bachelor of Science (BS)

2020 - Now

COMSATS Institute of Information Technology, Wah

Pakistan, Rawalpindi

BS Computer Science

Skills	
Firebase	****
NodeJS	****
HTTP's	****
Push Notifications	****
SqLite	****
Hive	****
Google Maps	****
Stripe Payment Integra- tion	****
Provider	****
Bloc (Cubit)	****
CI/CD (Github Actions)	*** *